{
    "subject": "resource/General_paresis_of_the_insane",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Sexually_transmitted_diseases_and_infections",
    "human_readable": "The topic of General paresis of the insane is Sexually transmitted diseases and infections.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9297134280204773,
            "question": "Is General paresis of the insane caused by a sexually transmitted disease?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8935979604721069,
            "question": "Can infections spread through sexual contact lead to General paresis of the insane?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8482208251953125,
            "question": "What is the topic of General paresis of the insane?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7304370999336243,
            "question": "What category of diseases does General paresis of the insane belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6706346273422241,
            "question": "How is General paresis of the insane diagnosed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6390634775161743,
            "question": "What are the symptoms of General paresis of the insane?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5508939623832703,
            "question": "Are there any preventive measures for contracting the disease that causes General paresis of the insane?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5485347509384155,
            "question": "Are there any treatments for General paresis of the insane?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5363008975982666,
            "question": "What historical context surrounds the understanding of General paresis of the insane?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5207938551902771,
            "question": "How has our understanding of General paresis of the insane evolved over time?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The topic of General paresis of the insane is Sexually transmitted diseases and infections.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1729_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What historical context surrounds the understanding of General paresis of the insane?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1729_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any treatments for General paresis of the insane?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1729_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any preventive measures for contracting the disease that causes General paresis of the insane?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1729_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1729_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1729_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1729_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1729_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1729_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1729_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1729_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1729_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1729_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1729_81.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents supports that general paresis of the insane (also known as neurosyphilis) is related to sexually transmitted diseases and infections, specifically syphilis. Therefore, the statement \"The topic of General paresis of the insane is Sexually transmitted diseases and infections\" is correct according to the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "General paresis of the insane is a complication due to untreated syphilis, which can be sexually transmitted but is not exclusively so. It can also be spread through non-sexual contact such as mother-to-child transmission during pregnancy and childbirth or by sharing infected needles in intravenous drug use.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}